{
    "id": "c731934cdccf4526b7a94bb440768d3f",
    "title": "Sentence Completion Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "................................... having many shortcomings, she is a nice woman at heart.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "In spite of",
                "Despite of",
                "Although"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "...................................... being a statesman, Winston Churchill was a writer.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "In spite of",
                "Besides",
                "Beside"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "..................................... having a lot of money, he leads a miserable life.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Although",
                "In spite",
                "Despite"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "They .................................... decided to disperse the meeting.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "unanimous",
                "unanimously"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": ".................................... on tip-toe, he reached for the apple.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Standing",
                "Stood"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The rain .................................... stopped, we continued our journey.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "had",
                "have",
                "having"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "She will .................................... come.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "certainly",
                "surely"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The chairman ....................................... taken his seat, the meeting began.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "have",
                "having",
                "had"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "It is your duty ................................... your brother.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "helping",
                "to help"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "................................. a noise, the thief ran away.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Hearing",
                "Heard",
                "Having hearing"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}